Finding Aid for the USA for Africa Records LSC.1669
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Burkina Faso / Cameroon, 1985-1990
  - Sahel Solidarite (Box 84, Folder 17-20)
    - Financial information - 01404. (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Progress report - 01404 [empty]. (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - S.O.S.-S.I./B.F. (Box 84, Folder 21-24)
    - Correspondence - 01405. (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - 01405. (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Financial information - 01405. (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Progress report - 01405. (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Groupement Naam (Box 85, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence - 01406. (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 01406. (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 01406. (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Progress report - 01406. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - World Relief (Box 85, Folder 5-8)
    - Correspondence - 01407. (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Project summary - 01407. (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - 01407. (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Progress report - 01407. (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Burkina Faso. (Box 85, Folder 9-10)
    - Country background. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings. (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - P.A.I.D. (Box 85, Folder 11-15)
    - Proposals - BG 610. (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Progress report - BG 610. (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Training program descriptions - BG 610. (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Financial information - BG 610. (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - BG 610. (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Family Health International (Box 85, Folder 16-20)
    - Correspondence - 11303. (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Reports - 11303. (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Proposals & grant application - 11303. (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Budget - 11303. (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Cameroon - Procurement - 11303. (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Chad / Mali, 1985-1990
  - C.A.R.E. (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence - 04003. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Financial information - 04003. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - International Service (UNAIS) (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - 04004. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Project summary - 04004. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Financial information - 04004. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Africare (Box 49, Folder 6-11)
    - Correspondence - 04005. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Project summary - 04005. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Financial information - 04005. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - 04006. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 04006. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Project summary - 04006. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - A.F.S.C. (Box 49, Folder 12-14)
    - Correspondence - 04007. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 04007. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 04007. (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - O.M.A.E.S. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - 04008. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - 04008. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Project summary - 04008. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Progress report - 04008. (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) / U.S. (Box 49, Folder 19-21)
    - Project summary - 04009. (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - 04009. (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - 04009. (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - International Service (UNAIS) (Box 49, Folder 22-23)
    - Correspondence - 04010. (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Project summary - 04010. (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Ethiopia, 1985-1990
  - E.R.C. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - no.03504. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - no.03504. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Ethipoia - R&RR - Jenden Association. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Christian Relief and Development Association (CRDA)- Jenden Associates (financial) - R&R I. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Sacow (Box 41, Folder 6-9)
    - Financial information - no.UD031001. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Progress report [empty]. (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - no.UD031001. (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Project summary - no.UD031001. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Ethiopia - C.R.D.A. program activities. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Christian Relief and Development Association (CRDA)- Program activities. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - S.A.F.T.E. (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
    - South African Refugee Scholarships. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Proposal. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - C.P.A.R. (Box 41, Box 42)
    - Correspondence - 03401. (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Project summary - 03401. (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - 03401. (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Progress report - 03401. (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Proposal summary - 03401. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - F.G.A. (Box 42, Folder 3-8)
    - Project summary - 03405. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - 03405. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - 03405. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Progress report - 03405. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Unfoldered material. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Christian Relief and Development Association (CRDA) (Box 42, Folder 2, 9-11)
    - Progress report - 03402. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - no.03710. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - no.03710. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Project summary - no.03710. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Ethiopia press. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Ethipoia - Non-governmental organizations (Community/association) (unfoldered material). (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - M.E.D.A.E. (Box 42, Folder 14-17)
    - Project summary - 03407. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Progress report - 03407. (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - 03407. (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - 03407. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Oxfam/UK (Box 42, Box 43)
    - Correspondence - 03408. (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Progress report - no.03408. (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Project summary - no.03408. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Financial information - no.03408. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Oxfam/America (Box 43, Folder 3-6)
    - Correspondence - 03409. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Project summary - 03409. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Financial information - 03409. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Ethiopia - RRC - "Grant Agreement" - 03001. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - RRC - Progress report - 03001. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Concern (Box 43, Folder 9-14)
    - Correspondence - 03002. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - 03002. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - 03002. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 03002. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 03003. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - 03003. (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Africare (Box 43, Folder 15-17)
    - Correspondence - 03004. (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Project summary - 03004. (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Financial information - 03004. (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - A.I.C.F. (Box 43, Folder 18-21)
    - Project summary - 03005. (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Financial information - 03005. (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Progress report - 03005. (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - 03005. (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - U.N.I.C.E.F. (Box 43, Folder 22-28)
    - Project summary - 03006. (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Financial information - 03006. (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - 03006. (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - 03007. (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Project summary - 03007. (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Financial information - 03007. (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - F.F.H. (Box 43, Folder 29-32)
    - Progress report - 03008. (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Financial information - 03008. (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Project summary - 03008. (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence - 03008. (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Ethiopia / Chad, 1985-1990
  - M.E.D.A.E. (Box 44, Folder 1-4)
    - Progress report - 03009. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Economic development - 03009. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Economic development - Project summary - 03009. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Financial information - 03009. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - American Joint Distribution Committee (Box 44, Folder 5-7)
    - Project summary - 03010. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - 03010. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - 03010. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Street Children Center (Box 44, Folder 8-9, 11)
    - Financial information - 03011. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - 03011. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - 03011. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Save the Children Fund (SCF) / U.S. - Progress report - 03011. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Ethiopia (Box 44, Folder 12-21)
    - HNA01 - Correspondence. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - HNA01 - Financial information. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - HNA01 - Project summary. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Country background. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Ethiopian organizations. (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Communications to Ethiopia. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Newsclippings. (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Non-governmental organizations/Community/Associations. (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Christian Relief & Development Association. (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Eritrea. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Unfoldered material. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Chad - R&RR (Box 45, Folder 3-16)
    - Euro-Action - 02103. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Red Cross - IHAP - 02104. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Red Cross - 02105. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - United Nations/Office of Equal Opportunity and Access - 02106. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - United Nations Disaster Relief Office (UNDRO) (Project Chad) - R&RR - 02107. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - World Food Programme (WFP) - 02108. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - World Vision - 02109. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - World Vision - 02109. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - World Vision - 02110. (Box 45, Folder 11-12)
    - CARE - 02111. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - A.I.C.F. - 02101. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - A.I.C.F. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Chad emergency funds - R&RR - Africare - 02102. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Final report - Africare - Chad - 02102. (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - American Red Cross - Reports. (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - R&RR - Report - Euro-action. (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - World Concern. (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Agence Europenne pour le Dveloppement et la Sant (AEDES) (Box 45, Folder 21-24)
    - Correspondence - 02392. (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Budget - 02302. (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 02302. (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Reports - 02302. (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - A.I.C.F. (Box 45, Box 46)
    - Correspondence - 02001. (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Financial information - 02001. (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Project summary - 02001. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - A.C.R.A.A.L. (Box 46, Folder 2-6)
    - Correspondence - 01999. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 01999. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Project summary - 01999. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Progress report - 01999. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - U.N.I.C.E.F. (Box 46, Folder 6-8)
    - Correspondence - 02003. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - 02003. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Project summary - 02003. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - World Concern (Box 46, Folder 9-11)
    - Correspondence - 02004. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - 02004. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - 02004. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - World Vision (Box 46, Folder 12-14)
    - Correspondence - 02005. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 02005. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 02005. (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Africare (Box 46, Folder 15-20)
    - Project summary - 02006. (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - 02006. (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - 02006. (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 02007. (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Project summary - 02007. (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - 02007. (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - V.I.T.A. (Box 46, Folder 21-22)
    - Correspondence - 02008. (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Financial information - 02008. (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - A.P.I.C.A. (Box 46, Folder 23-26)
    - Correspondence - 02401. (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 02401. (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Project summary - 02401. (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Progress report - 02401. (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Baha'i (Box 46, Folder 27-29)
    - Correspondence - 02402. (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Project summary - 02402. (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Financial information - 02402. (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - C.B.S.H.D. - Progress report - 02402. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - C.A.R.E./Chad (Box 47, Folder 2-4)
    - Financial information - 02403. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - 02403. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Project summary - 02403. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - C.A.R.E. - Progress report - 02403. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - C.E.D.E.S.C.O. (Box 47, Folder 6-8)
    - Correspondence - 02404. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Project summary - 02404. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Financial information - 02404. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - l'Institut Africain pour le Devloppement Economique et Social (Box 47, Folder 9-12)
    - Project summary - 02405. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 02405. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Progress report - 02405. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - 02405. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Oxfam/Secadev (Box 47, Folder 13-15)
    - Correspondence - 02406. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Project summary - 02406. (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - 02406. (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Progress report - 02406. (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - A.I.C.F. (Box 47, Folder 16-18)
    - Project summary - 02407. (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - 02407. (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 02407. (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - World Concern (Box 47, Folder 19-23)
    - Correspondence - 02408. (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Financial information - 02408. (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Project summary - 02408. (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Progress report - 02408. (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Ethiopia / Chad / Mali, 1985-1990
  - World Neighbors (Box 47, Box 48)
    - Correspondence - 02409. (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 02409. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 02409. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Progress report - 02409. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - l'Institut Africain pour le Devloppement Economique et Social (Box 48, Folder 4-7)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.02901. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.02901. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.02901. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Other - no.02WD927. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Mali (Box 48, Folder 8-15)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - R&RR - General. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - R&RR - Report - Africare. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - R&RR - Africare - 04101. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - R&RR - Africare - 04102. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - R&RR - U.N.I.C.E.F. - 04104. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - U.N.I.C.E.F. - Progress report - 04104. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - R&RR - U.N.D.R.O. - 04103. (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Progress report - U.N.D.R.O. (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - A.F.S.C. (Box 48, Folder 17-19)
    - Correspondence - 04001. (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - 04001. (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Project summary - 04001. (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - A.L.A.D. (Box 48, Folder 20-22)
    - Correspondence - 04002. (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - 04002. (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - 04002. (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - C.A.R.E. - Project summary - 04003. (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mali, 1985-1990
  - A.N.I.T.O.U. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 04011. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - 04011. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - 04011. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - V.S.F. (Box 50, Folder 4-6)
    - Financial information - 04012. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - 04012. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - 04012. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Association Kilabo (Box 50, Folder 7-10)
    - Correspondence - 04401. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Project summary - 04401. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Financial information - 04401. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Progress report - 04401. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - C.A.R.E., Incorporated (Box 50, Folder 11-14)
    - Correspondence - 04402. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 04402. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Financial information - 04402. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Progress report - 04402. (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - A.M.A.R.D. (Box 50, Folder 15-18)
    - Correspondence - 04403. (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Project summary - 04403. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Financial information - 04403. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Progress report - 04403. (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Accord (Box 50, Folder 19-21)
    - Correspondence - 04404. (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Financial information - 04404. (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Project summary - 04404. (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Promo Sahel (Box 50, Folder 22-25)
    - Correspondence - 04405. (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Project summary - 04405. (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Financial information - 04405. (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Promo-S - Progress report - 04405. (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - V.S.F. (Box 51, Folder 1-4)
    - Financial information - 04406. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 04406. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Project summary - 04406. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Progress report - 04406. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - O.M.A.E.S. (Box 51, Folder 5-8)
    - Correspondence - 04407. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - 04407. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Project summary - 04407. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Progress report - 04407. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Centre for Development and Population Activities (CEDPA) (Box 51, Folder 9-12)
    - Correspondence - 04408. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 04408. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Project summary - 04408. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Progress report - 04408. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Groupes Jeunes (Box 51, Folder 13-15)
    - Progress report - 04901. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.04901. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.04901. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.04901. (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - F.E.D.E.V. (Box 51, Folder 17-20)
    - Other - no.04WD931 [empty]. (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.04903. (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.04903. (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.04903. (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - F.E.D.E.V./W.E./T.O.T.O.T.O. (Box 52, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.04904. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.04904. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.04904. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Progress report - W.I.D. no.04904. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Mali (Box 52, Folder 5-8)
    - Correspondence - HNA05. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Financial information - HNA05. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Project summary - HNA05. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Proposal. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - A.M.R.A.D. (Box 52, Folder 9-12)
    - Correspondence - 04702. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Financial information. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Project summary - 04702. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Progress report [empty]. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - C.C.A./O.N.G. (Box 52, Folder 13-14)
    - Financial information - no.04706. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - no.04706. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - S.T.O.P.-Sahel (Box 52, Folder 15-17)
    - Project summary - no.04707. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Financial information - no.04707. (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - no.04707. (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Family Health International (Box 52, Folder 18-20)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 04302. (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Budget - 04302. (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Procurement - Mali - 04302. (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mali / Niger, 1985-1990
  - Family Health International - Reports - 04302. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - U of R (Box 53, Folder 2-5)
    - Reports - 04201. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - U of R/Bamako - Correspondence - 04201. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 04201. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Budget - 04201. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Non-governmental organizations/Community/Associations - Mali. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Oxfam/U.S. (Box 53, Folder 7-9)
    - Project summary - W.I.D. no.04902. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Financial information - W.I.D. no.04902. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - W.I.D. no.04902. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - M.S.F. (Box 53, Box 54)
    - Correspondence - 07302. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Proposal & Grant Application - 07302. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Report - 07302. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Budget - 07302. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Niger (Box 54, Folder 2-8)
    - Emergency funds (R&RR) - General. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Progress report - United Nations Development Programme - 7102. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - R&RR - United Nations Development Programme - 07102. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - R&RR - World Food Programme (WFP) - 07103. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Partial - Progress report. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Country background. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Cooperative League of the U.S.A. (CLUSA) (Box 54, Folder 9-12)
    - Correspondence - 07401. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Financial information - 07401. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Progress report - 07401. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Project summary - 07401. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - French Association of Volunteers of Progress (Box 54, Folder 13-16)
    - Project summary - 07402. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Financial information - 07402. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Progress report - 07402. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - 07402. (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - I.R.E.D./S.E.A.G. - All available papers - 07403. (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - O.P.C. (Box 54, Folder 18-20)
    - Correspondence - 07404. (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Project summary - 07404. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Financial information - 07404. (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Tufts (Box 54, Folder 21-26)
    - Correspondence - 07405. (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - 07405. (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Financial information - 07405. (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Progress report - 07405. (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Tufts U/U of Niamey - Niger health and nutrition surveillance training - 07405. (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Unfoldered Material - Project summary - 07405 [green binder]. (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Proposals Accepted & Funded - Mali / Niger / Senegal, 1985-1990
  - Niger country folder. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Africare (Box 55, Folder 2-12)
    - Correspondence - 07001. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Project summary - 07001. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Financial information - 07001. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Project summary - 07002. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - 07002. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Financial information - 07002. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Progress reports - 07002. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - 07003. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Project summary - 07003. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Financial information - 07003. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Progress report - 07003. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - C.A.R.E. (Box 55, Folder 13-15)
    - Correspondence - 07004. (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Financial information - 07004. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Project summary - 07004. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - I.L.O. (Box 55, Folder 16-19)
    - Financial information - 07005. (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Project summary - 07005. (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - 07005. (Box 55, Folder 18-19)
  - French Association of Volunteers of Progress (Box 55, Folder 20-22)
    - Correspondence - 07006. (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Financial information - 07006. (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Project summary - 07006. (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - C.A.R.E. (Box 55, Folder 23-25)
    - Correspondence - 07007. (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Project summary - 07007. (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Financial information - 07007. (Box 55, Folder 25)